30 days. 678 games. 10,000 miles! Are you game?
Nintendo Quest is a documentary film directed by Robert McCallum.
Homer's Odyssey meets King of Kong as two über geeks try to collect all 678 officially licensed Nintendo
Entertainment System game cartridges in 30 days, WITHOUT the aid of online purchasing.
Self, played by Jay Bartlett.
Self, played by Robert McCallum.
Self, played by Billy Mitchell.
Self, played by Walter Day.
Self, played by Patrick Scott Patterson.
Self, played by Rachel lara.
Nintendo Quest: The Most Unofficial and Unauthorized Nintendo Documentary Ever!
is a 2015 Canadian/American documentary road film directed by Rob McCallum about Jay Bartlett and his quest to acquire all 678
licensed Nintendo Entertainment System games within the span of 30 days, without purchasing any games online.
The film explores themes of video game, game, quest.